(this.webpackJsonptrivia=this.webpackJsonptrivia||[]).push([[0],{27:function(e,t,r){},28:function(e,t,r){},35:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var i=r(1),n=r(0),c=r.n(n),a=r(16),o=r.n(a),s=(r(27),r(28),r(17)),h=r(18),l=r(10),d=r(21),u=r(20),b=[{id:1,question:"Which is the biggest planet in the solar system?",choice1:"Earth",choice2:"Venus",choice3:"Saturn",choice4:"Jupiter",answer:"Jupiter",correct:"Correct! Jupiter is the biggest planet in the solar system.",incorrect:"Incorrect! Jupiter is the biggest planet in the solar system."},{id:2,question:"Which animal can hold its breath the longest?",choice1:"Seal",choice2:"Whale",choice3:"Sea Turtle",choice4:"Polar Bear",answer:"Sea Turtle",correct:"Correct! Sea Turtles can hold their breath for 4-10 hrs underwater.",incorrect:"Incorrect, Sea Turtles can hold their breath for 4-10 hrs underwater."},{id:3,question:"The word planet comes from the Greek word planete, which means-",choice1:"Divine",choice2:"Wanderer",choice3:"Sphere",choice4:"Bright",answer:"Wanderer",correct:"Correct! The word Planet is from the Greek word planetes which means Wanderers",incorrect:"Incorrect, The word Planet is from the Greek word planetes which means Wanderers"},{id:4,question:"Which philosopher coined the term 'I think, therefore I am'?",choice1:"Plato",choice2:"Aristotle",choice3:"Socrates",choice4:"Descartes",answer:"Descartes",correct:"Correct! Descartes was a french philosopher, widely regarded as one of the founders of modern philosophy",incorrect:"Incorrect! Descartes coined the term 'I think therefore I am'"},{id:5,question:"Which two U.S states do not observe Daylight saving?",choice1:"Arizona & Hawaii",choice2:"California & Oregon",choice3:"Maine & Rhode Island",choice4:"Florida & Texas",answer:"Arizona & Hawaii",correct:"Correct! Arizona & Hawaii do not observe daylight saving due to their hot weather",incorrect:"Incorrect! Arizona & Hawaii do not observe daylight saving due to their hot weather"},{id:6,question:"How many moon landings have there been?",choice1:"1",choice2:"6",choice3:"3",choice4:"7",answer:"6",correct:"Correct! The United States' Apollo 11 was the first crewed mission to land on the Moon, on 20 July 1969.There were six crewed U.S. landings between 1969 and 1972",incorrect:"Incorrect! The United States' Apollo 11 was the first crewed mission to land on the Moon, on 20 July 1969.There were six crewed U.S. landings between 1969 and 1972"},{id:7,question:"Botanically speaking, which of these fruits is NOT a berry?",choice1:"Strawberry",choice2:"Banana",choice3:"Blueberry",choice4:"Concord Grape",answer:"Strawberry",correct:"Correct! Despite its name, the strawberry isn't a true berry. Neither is the raspberry or the blackberry!",incorrect:"Incorrect! Despite its name, the strawberry isn't a true berry. Neither is the raspberry or the blackberry!"},{id:8,question:"Which of the following is the world's best-selling book?",choice1:"The Lord of the Rings",choice2:"The Alchemist",choice3:"Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",choice4:"The Da Vinci Code",answer:"The Lord of the Rings",correct:"Correct! The Lord of the Rings is one of the best-selling books ever written, with over 150 million copies sold",incorrect:"Incorrect! The Lord of the Rings is one of the best-selling books ever written, with over 150 million copies sold"},{id:9,question:"Who is the author of Jurassic Park",choice1:"Frank Herbert",choice2:"Stephen King",choice3:"Michael Crichton",choice4:"H.G Wells",answer:"Michael Crichton",correct:"Correct! Jurassic Park was written by Michael Crichton, which was later adapted in to the blockbuster film 'Jurassic Park",incorrect:"Incorrect! Jurassic Park was written by Michael Crichton, which was later adapted in to the blockbuster film 'Jurassic Park'"},{id:10,question:"What was the name given to the ancient trade routes that connected the East and West of Eurasia?",choice1:"Gold Route",choice2:"Trade road",choice3:"Iron road",choice4:"Silk Road",answer:"Silk Road",correct:"Correct! The Silk Road derives its name from the lucrative trade in silk carried out along its length, beginning in the Han dynasty in China",incorrect:"Incorrect! The Silk Road derives its name from the lucrative trade in silk carried out along its length, beginning in the Han dynasty in China"},{id:11,question:"Which dog breed is the smallest of them all?",choice1:"Dachshund",choice2:"Chihuahua",choice3:"Pomeranian",choice4:"Shih Tzu",answer:"Chihuahua",correct:"Correct! The Chihuahua is the smallest breed of dog, and is named after the Mexican state of Chihuahua",incorrect:"The Chihuahua is the smallest breed of dog, and is named after the Mexican state of Chihuahua"},{id:12,question:"What is the coldest place in the universe?",choice1:"Boomerang Nebula",choice2:"Virgo",choice3:"Andromeda",choice4:"Ursa Major",answer:"Boomerang Nebula",correct:"Correct! The Boomerang Nebula is one degree Kelvin which is -458 degrees Fahrenheit and is colder than the background temperature of deep space",incorrect:"Incorrect! The Boomerang Nebula is one degree Kelvin which is -458 degrees Fahrenheit and is colder than the background temperature of deep space"},{id:13,question:"What was the Turing Test originally called?",choice1:"Artificial Intelligence test",choice2:"The imitation game",choice3:"Computer test ",choice4:"Minimum intelligent signal test",answer:"The imitation game",correct:"Correct! The Turing test, originally called the imitation game by Alan Turing in 1950,is a test of a machine's ability to exhibit intelligent behaviour equivalent to, or indistinguishable from, that of a human",incorrect:"Incorrect! The Turing test, originally called the imitation game by Alan Turing in 1950,is a test of a machine's ability to exhibit intelligent behaviour equivalent to, or indistinguishable from, that of a human"}],m=r(8),g=function(e){Object(d.a)(r,e);var t=Object(u.a)(r);function r(e){var i;return Object(s.a)(this,r),(i=t.call(this,e)).state={num:Math.floor(Math.random()*b.length),numArray:[],answer:"",result:"",score:0,color:"#98fb98"},i.nextPage=i.nextPage.bind(Object(l.a)(i)),i}return Object(h.a)(r,[{key:"changeColor",value:function(){var e=this.state.numArray.length,t=e>4?Math.abs(e-5):e,r=["turquoise","pink","skyblue","#F5F383","#98fb98"][t];this.setState({color:r}),console.log(t,r)}},{key:"nextPage",value:function(){for(var e=Math.floor(Math.random()*b.length),t=0;t<this.state.numArray.length;t++)for(;e===this.state.numArray[t];)e=Math.floor(Math.random()*b.length),t=0;this.setState({num:e,result:""}),this.changeColor()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=this.state.num,r=b[t].question,n=b[t].choice1,c=b[t].choice2,a=b[t].choice3,o=b[t].choice4,s=b[t].answer,h=b[t].correct,l=b[t].incorrect,d=this.state.result?"none":"inline-block",u=function(t){return e.setState({answer:t.target.value})};return Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"contain",children:Object(i.jsxs)("div",{className:"header1",style:{backgroundColor:this.state.color},children:[Object(i.jsx)("h5",{children:r}),Object(i.jsxs)("form",{onSubmit:function(t){if(t.preventDefault(),""===e.state.answer)alert("Please choose an option");else{e.state.answer===s?e.setState({result:h,score:e.state.score+1}):e.state.answer!==s&&e.setState({result:l});var r=e.state.numArray;r.push(e.state.num),e.setState({numArray:r,answer:""})}},children:[Object(i.jsxs)("ul",{type:"none",children:[Object(i.jsxs)("li",{children:[Object(i.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",checked:this.state.answer===n,name:"choice",onChange:u,value:n})," ".concat(n)]}),Object(i.jsxs)("li",{children:[Object(i.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",checked:this.state.answer===c,name:"choice",onChange:u,value:c})," ".concat(c)]}),Object(i.jsxs)("li",{children:[Object(i.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",checked:this.state.answer===a,name:"choice",onChange:u,value:a})," ".concat(a)]}),Object(i.jsxs)("li",{children:[Object(i.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",checked:this.state.answer===o,name:"choice",onChange:u,value:o})," ".concat(o)]})]}),Object(i.jsx)("button",{className:"butn",style:{display:d},type:"submit",children:"Submit"})]}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{children:this.state.result?Object(i.jsx)(j,{result:this.state.result,nextPage:this.nextPage,numArray:this.state.numArray,score:this.state.score}):""})]})})}}]),r}(n.Component);function j(e){return 10===e.numArray.length?Object(i.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(i.jsx)("p",{children:e.result}),Object(i.jsxs)("h5",{children:["Your Score is ".concat(e.score,"!")," "]}),Object(i.jsx)(m.b,{className:"link",to:"/",children:Object(i.jsx)("button",{className:"butn1",children:"Play Again"})})]}):Object(i.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(i.jsx)("p",{children:e.result}),Object(i.jsx)("button",{className:"butn",onClick:e.nextPage,children:"Next"})]})}var w=function(){return Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"contain",children:Object(i.jsxs)("div",{className:"header",children:[Object(i.jsx)("h1",{children:"Welcome to Trivia!"}),Object(i.jsx)(m.b,{className:"link",to:"/quest",children:Object(i.jsx)("button",{className:"butn",children:"Start"})})]})})},f=r(2);var p=function(){return Object(i.jsx)(m.a,{children:Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(i.jsxs)(f.c,{children:[Object(i.jsx)(f.a,{exact:!0,path:"/",render:function(){return Object(i.jsx)(w,{})}}),Object(i.jsx)(f.a,{path:"/quest",render:function(){return Object(i.jsx)(g,{})}})]})})})},y=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,36)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,i=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,c=t.getLCP,a=t.getTTFB;r(e),i(e),n(e),c(e),a(e)}))};r(34);o.a.render(Object(i.jsx)(c.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(i.jsx)(p,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),y()}},[[35,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.4034bcf9.chunk.js.map